The XRP price hasn't moved.
But the risk already has.
Most DeFi collateral controls wait for price data to reveal a crisis.
By then, lending markets may already be exposed.
This is RiskOracle, built for interoperable assets on Flare.
Watch the same XRP price as a regulatory shock arrives.
A price-only oracle still reads low.
RiskOracle sends the headline to four independent models.
GPT-5.5 scores 92, Claude Opus 85, DeepSeek 95, and Qwen3 85.
Consensus: 89, before the market reprices.
The models never see one another's answers.
RiskOracle exposes their spread and applies divergence-aware consensus, making uncertainty visible instead of hiding it.
The pipeline begins with Flare FTSOv2 market state.
AI adds event, liquidity, volatility, and contagion context.
Because model output is non-deterministic, RiskOracle freezes the result into deterministic JSON for FDC Web2Json attestation.
Here is the proof: deployed Coston2 contracts, immutable RiskUpdated events, and a successful end-to-end FDC transaction.
Continuous demo updates use a lightweight signer; the full FDC path is already proven on-chain.
At risk 95, the FXRP lending example suspends new borrowing, and the insurance pool stops new underwriting.
One signal; policy remains with each protocol.
Built from scratch during Flare Summer Signal.
RiskOracle: verifiable risk intelligence for interoperable assets, before price reacts.